https://www.rokpa.org/service/privacy-statement.html

What we doNepalChildren's HomeSoup Kitchen & Medical AmbulatoryWomen's WorkshopGuest HouseHospitality TrainingEarthquake ReliefAfricaZimbabweHelping KidsDrop-In CentersGardening ProjectsSouth AfricaSoup KitchenCircle of NourishmentPermacultureTibetan Areas of ChinaEducationPrimary and secondary schoolUniversity EducationMonastery schoolsLiteracy for young adultsMedical AidBasic Medical CareMedical Emergency AidTraditional Tibetan MedicineFood/Living CostsROKPA Emergency Food ProgramWho we areWhy ROKPA?OrganisationBoardHeadquartersPatronageFoundersCore ValuesMilestones40 Years of ROKPAROKPA NetworkCanadaDeutschlandEspañaEuskadiGreat BritainIrelandItaliaNederlandNepalÖsterreichPolskaSouth AfricaSwitzerlandUSAZimbabweSupportersPublicationsAnnual ReportVideosFAQsWhat you can doDonate NowSponsor a themeEducationMedical AidFood/Living CostsChildrenGirls and WomenUrgent ROKPA projectsSubscribe nowDonors in action for ROKPAWills and TestamentsVolunteering & Donations in KindBuy and helpROKPA ShopWal-Ro-PuppetsWaldorfplaygroupWaldorfkindergartenCuddly Series 2020Vegan Waldorf PuppetsMia, Mio and BabyDoll Changing SetDolly Baby CarriersSchellen-UrsliOther itemsGift a project sponsorshipNewsFacebook-FeedNewsletterChange Language (English)DeutschFrançaisEnglish
ROKPA INTERNATIONALBöcklinstrasse 278032 ZurichSwitzerlandPhone +41 44 262 68 88Mail: info (at) rokpa.org
IBAN CH73 0483 5045 5090 1100 1
NewsletterROKPA Network
ROKPA Guest House
ROKPA Women's Workshop
Contact
Newsletter
ROKPA Network
Change Language
Deutsch | Français | English
What we doNepalChildren's HomeSoup Kitchen & Medical AmbulatoryWomen's WorkshopGuest HouseHospitality TrainingEarthquake ReliefAfricaZimbabweSouth AfricaTibetan Areas of ChinaEducationMedical AidFood/Living CostsROKPA Emergency Food ProgramWho we areWhy ROKPA?OrganisationBoardHeadquartersPatronageFoundersCore ValuesMilestones40 Years of ROKPAROKPA NetworkCanadaDeutschlandEspañaEuskadiGreat BritainIrelandItaliaNederlandNepalÖsterreichPolskaSouth AfricaSwitzerlandUSAZimbabweSupportersPublicationsAnnual ReportVideosFAQsWhat you can doDonate NowSponsor a themeEducationMedical AidFood/Living CostsChildrenGirls and WomenUrgent ROKPA projectsSubscribe nowDonors in action for ROKPAWills and TestamentsVolunteering & Donations in KindBuy and helpROKPA ShopWal-Ro-PuppetsGift a project sponsorshipNewsFacebook-FeedNewsletter
Donate now!
SitemapPrivacy Statement
ROKPA Privacy Statement
General
Your privacy is very important to us. ROKPA adheres strictly to the statutory data protection rules.
Use of donor information
As a donor or subscriber to the newsletter, you can decide for yourself which personal information you wish to share with us. You can also determine in which cases we are allowed to contact you and in which form. Based on the information you provide, we will inform you in writing or via E-Mail of developments within ROKPA projects. We will also need your address to issue a donation receipt.
ROKPA will only use your personal information for internal purposes and will not pass it on to third parties. ROKPA has its own database and manages the addresses itself. We do not lease or sell any addresses.
Deletion from mailing list possible at any time
At your request we will remove your data from our mailing list. You can request this at any time without stating a reason, via E-Mail (info (at) rokpa.org) or telephone (+41 (0)44 262 68 88). You will not be contacted by us again after this time.
Copyright for images and texts
ROKPA INTERNATIONAL holds the copyright for texts and images published on this website. Any commercial reproduction and/or use is only possible with the consent of ROKPA. © ROKPA INTERNATIONAL and the website www.rokpa.org must be cited as the source.
Protection of trademarks and logos
The names ROKPA and ROKPA INTERNATIONAL are protected trademarks. These names and the ROKPA logo may only be used with the written consent of ROKPA.
Content of external links
ROKPA assumes no liability whatsoever for the content of external links. The operators of the linked pages are exclusively responsible for the content.
Analysis of website usage
This website uses Google Analytics, a service provided by Google Inc. The information obtained will not however be linked with any personal information. Direct identification of your use of our website is therefore not possible.
